{
    "subject": "resource/Josefus",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Josefus was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8654059171676636,
            "question": "Where was Josefus born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8512498140335083,
            "question": "When was Josefus born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.650503396987915,
            "question": "Was Josefus born in a big city or a small town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.632469654083252,
            "question": "What nationality is Josefus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5452868342399597,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance related to Josefus's birth place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5174093246459961,
            "question": "What country is Josefus from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4244716763496399,
            "question": "What is Josefus known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41332337260246277,
            "question": "Is Josefus a well-known person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26572567224502563,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Josefus's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2328813076019287,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Josefus?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josefus was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9333_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you have any information about Josefus's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9333_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Josefus a well-known person?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9333_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Josefus known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9333_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9333_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not support the triple that Josefus was born in the United States. The documents mention various places and dates of birth for a person named Josephus or Josefus, but none of them indicate that he was born in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information about Josefus (Josephus) being born in the United States. All provided information pertains to his birthplace as Jerusalem, which is in Judaea during Roman times, and does not mention the U.S."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}